

KAVYA NORI

CONSULTANT

CONTACT

+1 514 778 2330

KAVYA.NORI@GMAIL.COM



- Analytics
- Customer Service
- Team Worker
- Ouick Learner
- Project Management
- Effective Research Skills

SOFTWARE

- Excel
- SAP BI
- SQL Server
- Crystal Reports
- SAP Predictive Analytics
- SAP MDG
- SAP Lumira
- Adobe
- PowerPoint
- R Studio

PROGRAMMING

- C/C++
- Java
- ABAP
- Python
- HTML5
- SQL/T-SQL



fb.com/kavya.nori



kavyanori



@krsna2498

2 PROFILE

I am an experienced ERP Techno Functional Consultant with a background in engineering. I have rich experience of primary research through qualitative and quantitative data analysis. I am a great team player with excellent interpersonal and communications skills, who thrives on bringing value to the business while taking up new challenges and learning new skills.

EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT CONSULTANT

APEX TECHNOLOGY INNOVATIONS | MAR 2016 - PRESENT

- Use data analysis to compare the company with peers and also bring in new clients.
- Increased social media following and clicks by 200%

MIS SUPPORT - LEVEL 2

GROUPE HYPERTEC | MAR 2015 - NOV 2015

- Create Crystal Reports and SQL Queries to extract and manipulate for day-to-day data from the CRM.
- Create Users and Authorizations in SAP Business One and Microsoft Dynamics CRM.

SAP BI DEVELOPER

FUJIFILM | SEP 2014 - FEB 2015

- Extract, Transform and Load data from various data sources and manipulate data using ABAP and SQL.
- Create reports for company-wide usage for various business cases and enable better sales.

ASSOCIATE BUSINESS CONSULTANT

SAP INDIA | OCT 2012 - AUG 2014

- Created prototype for Telecommunications analysis between Service Providers to increase sales using R, SAP HANA and Predictive Analytics.
- Part of various development, testing, support and training teams in SAP ABAP, SAP MDG and SAP Predictive Analytics.



EDUCATION .

B.TECH,, ELEC. & COMM. ENGINEERING JNTU | 2008 - 2012



AWARDS AND CERTIFICATIONS

BEST OUTGOING STUDENT AWARD

HIGH SCHOOL - MARCH 2006

SAP CERTIFIED DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATE - ABAP WITH SAP **NETWEAVER 7.31**

SAP - MARCH 2013

OUTSTANDING ACHIEVEMENT AWARD

SAP - DECEMBER 2013